Another thing to remember,
还要注意的一个事项是
is that journals themselves impose their own editorial influence on papers too.
期刊本身也会对论文带来编辑影响
They look for papers of certain types.
他们会寻找特定类型的论文
They ask for papers to be structured in certain ways.
要求论文采用一定的结构
They impose word counts and style guides.
会提出字数和风格要求
Often within a field,
通常 在某个领域
certain journals are known to be the most competitive to
发表到某些期刊上竞争很激烈
get your work published in and the most high profile.
并且关注度最高
Typically these journals have the largest most diverse readership.
这些期刊通常拥有最广泛的读者群
So, a paper must be of sufficient importance and
所以论文必须足够重要
broad interests to be published there and be circulated to the most eyeballs.
并且能吸引众多读者的兴趣 才能发表到这些期刊上
The other important thing I wanted to tell you is that,
还要一个重要事项是
if what you are trying to do is understand
如果你想了解整个领域
a whole field and not just an individual experiment,
而不是某个实验或项目
or project, what you may want is a review paper.
建议阅读综述论文
This is a paper that has a different purpose.
这种论文的目标不一样
It's meant to be a summary,
它是对关于同一主题的
or discussion of several papers,
多篇论文
or ideas on the same topic.
或多个观点的总结
These are like gold for newcomers to a field.
这些论文对新手来说就像黄金一样
It's not always clear where and how to find them.
有时候不知道去哪找 如何寻找
Sometimes a journal that normally publishes regular papers puts out an issue of reviews.
有些平常发布普通论文的期刊会发布一期综述论文
Other times you'll find helpful reviews and journals that only publish reviews.
有些期刊专门发布综述论文
For example, the journal annual reviews.
例如《Annual Reviews》期刊
A final thing to know,
最后一个事项是
when you are reading research papers is that,
研究论文是一种
yes a paper is a piece of communication or documentation about a study.
传递研究成果的方式
But it is also an assertion that science has progressed,
但是也表明科学发展了
that knowledge has advanced,
知识进步了
in other words it's an assertion that the work
也就是说 研究记录的成果
documented in the study means something important about the world.
对世界来说很重要
When a paper is complete enough to be sent to a journal,
当论文已经完毕 可以提交给期刊时
it usually means that many people think the work is valid and meaningful.
通常表明有很多人认为研究成果是有效和有意义的
The lead author, her colleagues, her adviser,
包括主要作者 她的同事
and potentially other people in
她的导师
the research community who the person showed the work to or discuss it with.
以及参与讨论的其他人
But then when a journal editor takes interest in a paper,
但是当期刊编辑对论文感兴趣时
the work is usually sent out to other people who do similar work.
通常会将论文提供给其他有过类似成就的人
These people often raise very important concerns about
这些人经常对作品的有效性和意义提出重要的问题
the validity or meaning of the work that nobody else has mentioned yet.
任何其他人都没提过这类问题
Their assertions can block publication of the paper if not addressed.
如果没有解决这类问题 这些人的意见可能会阻止论文发表
This is the peer review process.
这就是同行评审流程
Finally, even after a paper is published,
最后 即使论文发表了
sometimes information comes out that cast the information in the paper in a new light.
有时候出现新的信息 对论文会有新的理解
For example, sometimes other researchers
例如 有时候其他研究者
try to do the same thing and get different results.
尝试完成相同的操作但是结果不一样
This isn't to say that you should necessarily always doubt the authors assertions,
这并不是说你应该始终怀疑作者的结论
but neither should you believe them wholesale.
但是也不能全盘相信
The reality is far more nuanced than that.
实际情况要复杂得多
The vast majority of the time,
大部分情况下
they did what they say they did but there may be a caveat about how they did
他们都按照所说的完成实验
it such that what they did is not as meaningful as they think,
但是对完成方式可能不够坦诚 并不像他们认为的那样有意义
this is just to say that the process of establishing
总之 知识发现过程很漫长
knowledge is long and has many twists and turns.
有很多波折
Remember that when you read a paper,
当你阅读论文时
you're somewhere in the middle of that process which is
也处在这种过程中 这也让人很兴奋
also rather exciting because when you're reading papers,
因为当你阅读论文时
you maybe learning about things that are so new
可能会学到一些新知识
that very few people in the world have heard of them yet.
世界上没有多少人知道这些知识
Getting back to the actual reading,
回到实际阅读问题上
sometimes it is important that you read an entire paper.
有时候需要阅读整篇论文
For example, if you're doing a presentation on it
例如 如果你要做演讲
and people are going to ask you detailed questions.
会有听众问你细节性问题
But more often there's certain information you are
但更多时候 你只想从论文中
looking to take from a paper and that's all you need.
发现特定信息
I think the most important thing to remember in practice is to keep up your momentum.
我认为最重要的一点是 不要气馁
Don't get stuck on a tiny detail that you don't understand.
不要拘泥于不明白的小细节
If you think it's really important,
如果你认为这个细节很重要的话
take a note and look it up elsewhere later and move on.
记下来 之后去别的地方查询并继续阅读论文